junglearcade.com 2017-12-07

# Jungle Arcade - Privacy

At www.junglearcade.com (referred to as "Company," "us" or "we"), we recognize that your privacy is important. This Policy discloses the privacy practices for the Company's website at www.junglearcade.com (collectively, the "Site”). This Policy also covers how personal and other information that we receive or collect about you is treated. Please read the information below to learn the following regarding your use of this Site. 

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is designed to be read in connection with the Site Terms and Conditions of Use, which is available at <http://www.junglearcade.com/terms>, and that by accessing or using our Site, you agree to be bound by the Site's terms and conditions, as well as this Policy. 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site and by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) your agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy. 

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**California Privacy Rights – Shine the Light Law**

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

  1. **Types of Information We Collect**

In order to better provide you with the Site, we collect two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") and Aggregate Information. 

_Personally Identifiable Information_

: This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on this Site, such as sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. 

Examples of PII may include your first and last name, email address, mailing address (including zip code), telephone and facsimile numbers, other identifying information that you provide to us if and when you contact us, and records and copies of your correspondence if you contact us. 

_Aggregate Information_ : This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our Site and what other sites may have directed you to us. The information we collect includes usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, and browsing actions and patterns. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. We may maintain Aggregate Information or associate Aggregate Information with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. This information may include information about your computer and internet connection, including what browser you are using, your operating system and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. We also collect information regarding the details of your visits t our Site, such as, the Website's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that points to the site you just came from, which URL you go to after visiting our Site, traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Site. 

  2. **How We Collect and Use Information**

We do not collect any PII about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us, such as by sending us an email message or submitting a form or transmitting other information by telephone or letter. 

We will primarily use your PII to provide customer support to you. We will also use certain forms of PII to provide the Site to you, recognize when you return to the Site, enhance the operation of our Site, improve our internal marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze Site use, improve our product and service offerings, customize our Site's content, layout, and services, contact you about our own and third-parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you, for any other purpose with you consent, and to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide us the information. We may use PII to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. Finally, we may use your PII to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Site Terms of Use, and this Privacy Policy. 

We may also collect, and our third party advertising partners may collect, certain Aggregate Information. For example, we may use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our Site and to gather demographic information. Our third party advertising partners may also provide us with aggregate, but not individual, reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon at out Site. 

**3\. Cookies, Flash Cookies and Web Beacons**

_Cookies_

Depending on how you use our Site, we will store cookies on your computer in order to collect certain aggregate data about our users and to customize certain aspects of your specific user experience. A cookie is a small data text file which is stored on your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Cookies may also include more personalized information, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server, and your first name to welcome you back to our Site. We may use cookies to perform tasks such as: monitoring aggregate site usage metrics, storing account and advertising preferences that you have set, and personalizing the Site. We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third ­party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). 

We may also use an outside advertising partner to display banner advertisements on our Site. As part of their service, they will place a separate cookie on your computer. We will not provide any third-party advertising partners with any of your PII. We and our third party ad server will collect and use Aggregate Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular ad. Other advertisers may also place banner ads on our Site in the same manner as above, but we will not disclose any PII to them. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some aspects of the Site may not function properly if you elect to disable cookies. 

_Flash Cookies_

Certain features of our Site may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Site. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see _Choices about How We Use and Disclose Your Information_ . 

_Web Beacons_

Pages of our the Site may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). 

  4. **Release of Information**

We may disclose Aggregate Information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. 

We may disclose PII that you provide as described in this privacy policy to: (i) our parents, subsidiaries and affiliates; (ii) contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business; (iii) a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, including as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about our Site users is among the assets transferred; (iv) to third parties to market their products or services to you; (v) fulfill the purpose for which you provide it; (vi) for any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information; (vii) with your consent. We may also disclose your personal information: (y) to enforce or apply our terms of use found at www.junglearcade.com/terms; or (z) if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Us, our customers or others. 

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide PII to the appropriate governmental authorities. In such cases, we will disclose PII upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation or administrative investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. 

We may also provide Aggregate Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related Site information to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information. 

  5. **Updating and Correcting Information**

We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the PII that you have provided to us. You may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by emailing us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Please include your name, address, and/or email address when you contact us. 

We encourage you to promptly update your PII if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, some information, such as past transactions, logs of technical support calls, or other information may not be deleted. In addition, it may be impossible to completely delete your information without some residual information because of backups. 

  6. **User Choices on Collection and Use of Information**

You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described above. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you choose to reject all cookies some parts of our Site may not work properly in your case. 

We do not respond to “Do Not Track” signals or frameworks requesting an alteration to our online tracking of individual users who visit our Site. 

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") on the NAI's website: [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

  7. **Security of Your PII**

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. 

  8. **Miscellaneous**

Our Site is not intended for persons under 18 years of age. No one under age 18 may provide any information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under 18. If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on this Site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a person under 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information if applicable law requires us to do so. If you believe we might have any information from or about a person under 18, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

If you have any questions, concerns or inquiries about our Privacy Policy, or our use of your PII, or our privacy practices, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
